- Why the gun? - We must bring him back.
- 총은 왜요? - 그를 다시 데려와야 해요.
We can never let them take him.
우리는 결코 그들이 그를 데려가도록 놔둘 수 없습니다.
If it can't be stopped...
멈출 수 없다면...
elimination is the only option.
제거만이 유일한 선택이다.
Yeah, Dad. I caught him.
응, 아빠. 나는 그를 잡았다.
"Caught"?
'잡혔다'?
I get it!
알겠습니다!
I will take care of it myself.
내가 직접 처리하겠습니다.
I shouldn't have come.
오지 말았어야 했는데.
Damn it.
젠장.
- Damn it. - I'm curious about something.
- 젠장. - 궁금한 게 있어요.
Can I ask?
물어봐도 될까요?
Why did you come here?
왜 여기에 왔나요?
I could kill you right now,
난 지금 당장 당신을 죽일 수도 있어요
and you wouldn't be able to fight back.
그리고 당신은 반격할 수 없을 것입니다.
It's not like I'd actually do it.
실제로 그렇게 할 것 같지는 않습니다.
I'm just saying I could.
나는 단지 할 수 있다고 말하고 있습니다.
- Do it. - Yes, ma'am.
- 해봐. - 네, 부인.
When you're done, just kill him.
다 끝나면 그를 죽여라.
I came here...
내가 여기 왔는데...
because I wanted a normal life.
나는 평범한 삶을 원했기 때문이다.
To do so...
그렇게 하려면...
I need to unite with the other superhumans
다른 슈퍼휴먼들과 연합해야 해
to fight against you
너와 싸우려고
and secure our safety...
우리의 안전을 확보하고...
rights, and interests.
권리, 이익.
What?
무엇?
I can't just sell something I inherited from my parents.
난 그냥 뭔가를 팔 수 없어 나는 부모님에게서 물려받았습니다.
Don't you agree?
동의하지 않나요?
Bun-mi. Now's the time.
분미. 지금이 바로 그때다.
The money.
돈.
Just kill him!
그냥 죽여라!
What the fuck happened?
대체 무슨 일이 일어난 거야?
Wanna know what happened?
무슨 일이 있었는지 알고 싶으신가요?
Well,
음,
I just followed my heart.
나는 내 마음을 따랐을 뿐입니다.
Ever since the truce, the Mundane Vanguard has been watching us.
휴전 이후부터 평범한 선봉대가 우리를 지켜보고 있었습니다.
MUNDANE
평범한
Given the circumstances,
상황에 따라
sneaking into their lab without drawing their attention
그들의 연구실에 몰래 들어가다 관심을 끌지 않고
seemed impossible.
불가능해 보였습니다.
The only way...
유일한 방법은...
Hey, Bun-mi.
안녕, 분미.
...was to deceive ourselves.
...우리 자신을 속이려는 것이었습니다.
Everyone, just follow your heart.
여러분, 마음을 따르세요.
Wait for the signal at the last moment.
마지막 순간에 신호를 기다리세요.
I trust you.
나는 당신을 믿습니다.
Hey, I almost died!
이봐, 나 거의 죽을뻔했어!
Who the hell came up with this absurd plan?
도대체 누가 나왔는지 이런 말도 안되는 계획으로?
Well, I couldn't trust you.
글쎄요, 난 당신을 믿을 수가 없었어요.
But you wrote "I trust you."
그런데 당신은 "나는 당신을 믿습니다"라고 썼습니다.
That was meant for Bun-mi.
그건 분미를 위한 것이었습니다.
Over there.
저기요.
There's the safe.
금고가 있어요.
You're good at opening safes now.
이제 금고를 잘 여는군요.
The first time's hard. The second? A breeze.
처음은 어렵습니다. 두 번째? 산들바람.
This is...
이것은...
BEOMHA RANCH
범하목장
The documents.
문서.
Hurry! Those guys are seriously...
서두르다! 그 사람들은 진심인데...
MY MIN-SUK
마이민석
Hey, what is it?
이봐, 그게 뭐야?
- Our parents' first meeting. - What?
- 우리 부모님의 첫 만남. - 무엇?
Our parents' meeting will be the day after tomorrow.
우리 부모님 모임 모레가 될 거예요.
The day after tomorrow? You're telling me this now?
모레? 지금 나한테 이런 말을 하는 거야?
I just found a coupon for a traditional Korean restaurant,
방금 쿠폰을 찾았어요 전통 한식당의 경우,
so I bought it.
그래서 샀어요.
It's 50% off.
50% 할인이에요.
Hey, wait.
잠깐만요.
Gosh. Wait a minute.
이런. 잠깐 기다려요.
No, my money!
아니, 내 돈!
Oh God. No.
오 맙소사. 아니요.
No!
안돼!
What? You don't like it?
무엇? 당신은 그것을 좋아하지 않습니까?
This place is really expensive. We can't go without a discount.
이 곳은 정말 비싸요. 우리는 할인 없이는 갈 수 없습니다.
All right, then.
그럼요.
It's a coupon, so no refunds.
쿠폰이라 환불은 안되네요.
Call your parents now and tell them.
지금 부모님에게 전화해서 말씀하세요.
Dinner on Friday at 7:00 p.m.
금요일 오후 7시에 저녁 식사.
Okay.
좋아요.
Jeez!
이런!
Sang-ung, let's go!
상웅아, 가자!
Okay.
좋아요.
Still got alcohol?
아직도 술을 마셨나요?
You got money?
돈 있어요?
If a superhuman has no superpowers,
초인에게 초능력이 없다면
they're just human.
그들은 단지 인간일 뿐입니다.
Now I kind of get what Dad meant.
이제 아빠가 무슨 말씀을 하셨는지 알겠습니다.
Superpowers?
초능력?
It's not a big deal.
별거 아닙니다.
BEOMHA RANCH
범하목장
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
She's seriously nuts.
그녀는 정말 미쳤어요.
Jeez.
이런.
- Hurry. - Let's get out.
- 서두르다. - 나가자.
Seriously.
진지하게.
Four billion won...
40억 원...
just vanished before my eyes.
방금 내 눈앞에서 사라졌다.
Being broke is nothing new to you.
파산하는 것은 당신에게 새로운 것이 아닙니다.
With four billion won...
40억 원으로…
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
Of course.
물론.
I am the Cashero, after all.
결국 나는 Cashero입니다.
You must be crazy.
당신은 미쳤음에 틀림없다.
These jerks have done some illegal experiments.
이 멍청이들이 해냈어 일부 불법 실험.
I'm not sure what they're after,
그들이 무엇을 쫓고 있는지 잘 모르겠습니다.
but they're doing something with our superpowers.
그런데 그 사람들 뭔가 하고 있는 것 같아 우리의 초능력으로.
A NEW BUSINESS MODEL UTILIZING DEPENDENCY AND HALLUCINATION
새로운 비즈니스 모델 의존성과 환각의 활용
What is it? What are they doing?
그것은 무엇입니까? 그들은 무엇을 하고 있나요?
It seems like they're going to make something.
그것은 것 같다 그들은 뭔가를 만들 것입니다.
"In the process of restoring the superpower protein..."
"복원 과정에서 초강력 단백질..."
Sang-ung.
상웅.
TO SANG-UNG
상웅에게
"I admire the way you work for others
"나는 당신이 다른 사람들을 위해 일하는 방식을 존경해요.
even without recognition."
인식하지 못하더라도."
"That's the kind of hero the world needs."
"이것이 바로 세상에 필요한 영웅이다."
"Jo Nathan."
"조 네이선."
Jo Nathan?
조 네이선?
You have a great name.
당신은 훌륭한 이름을 갖고 있습니다.
NAME: JO NATHAN
이름: 조 네이선
Mr. Jo Nathan.
미스터. 조 네이선.
I admire the way you work for others even without recognition.
나는 당신이 다른 사람들을 위해 일하는 방식을 존경합니다 인식하지 못하더라도.
The thing is,
문제는
I'm also working quietly to make a difference.
나도 조용히 일하고 있어 변화를 만들기 위해.
JO NATHAN
조 네이선
It's too bad, Jo Anna.
안타깝네요, 조안나.
Father would hate this.
아버지는 이것을 싫어하실 것입니다.
How does freedom feel?
자유는 어떤 느낌인가요?
Not bad.
나쁘지 않아요.
The chairman already moved them all.
회장님이 이미 다 옮겼어요.
To Gimhae Bank.
김해은행으로.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
What I want isn't here anyway.
어차피 내가 원하는 건 여기에 없어.
All set?
다 준비됐나요?
Yes, of course.
물론이죠.
Let's get started.
시작해 봅시다.
RESTRICTED AREA
제한 구역
RESIDENCY FORM APRIL 2025
거주 양식 2025년 4월
JO NATHAN UNIT 2302, CHANGIL PARKTRIUM
조 네이선 창일파크트리엄 2302호
Is this Jo Nathan's place?
여기가 Jo Nathan의 집인가요?
By the way, mister,
그런데 아저씨,
isn't it illegal for a civil servant to look into someone's address?
공무원 불법 아닌가요 누군가의 주소를 조사하려고?
Yes, it's illegal. Report me if you have a problem.
예, 불법입니다. 문제가 있으면 신고해주세요.
Get ready.
준비하세요.
Jesus!
예수!
No one's here.
여기에는 아무도 없습니다.
It seems like he hasn't moved in yet.
아직 입주하지 않은 것 같습니다.
He has.
그는 그랬다.
What?
무엇?
What is it? What's wrong?
그것은 무엇입니까? 무슨 일이야?
Wait a second.
잠깐만요.
Gosh!
이런!
My goodness! What's going on?
이럴 수가! 무슨 일이야?
It's him.
그 사람이에요.
Just like Whac-A-Mole,
두더지 잡기처럼
the moment you get rid of one crazy villain,
당신이 제거되는 순간 한 미친 악당의
a new creative one pops up.
새 광고 소재가 나타납니다.
STATEMENT OF HOUSING ACQUISITION FINANCING AND OCCUPANCY PLAN
주택 구입 자금 조달 명세서 및 점유 계획
REQUIRED DOCUMENT FOR REAL ESTATE TRANSACTION
필수서류 부동산 거래의 경우
REAL ESTATE TRANSACTION CORPORATE DECLARATION
부동산 거래 기업 선언문
Don't push yourself too hard.
너무 무리하지 마세요.
Have some rice and soup before bed.
자기 전에 밥과 국을 드세요.
It was your turn to cook tonight.
오늘 밤은 당신이 요리할 차례였습니다.
Come home early tomorrow.
내일 일찍 집에 오세요.
I wonder how all those superheroes in movies
저 많은 슈퍼히어로들은 어떻게 지내는지 궁금해요 영화에서
juggle beating up all the bad guys, keeping a family,
저글링으로 나쁜 놈들을 모두 물리치고, 가족을 부양하고,
and holding down a job?
일을 계속하고 계시나요?
I admire them.
저는 그들을 존경합니다.
It looks delicious.
맛있어 보이네요.
Mr. Kang.
강 선생님.
Seriously,
진지하게,
what on earth have you been doing for the police to come looking for you?
도대체 뭐하고 있었어? 경찰이 당신을 찾으러 올까요?
There was a minor misunderstanding.
사소한 오해가 있었습니다.
Give me a full report
전체 보고서를 보내주세요.
on your unauthorized vehicle use and leaving work early.
귀하의 무단 차량 사용에 대해 그리고 일찍 퇴근.
You'll face the disciplinary committee. Expect a pay cut as well.
징계위원회에 회부됩니다. 급여 삭감도 기대됩니다.
A pay cut?
급여 삭감?
Why?
왜?
Why else? It's the rule.
왜 또? 그것은 규칙입니다.
- It's for three months. - Three...
- 3개월이에요. - 세...
Three whole months?
3개월 내내요?
If my salary were cut by a third,
내 월급이 3분의 1로 삭감된다면
I'd barely meet the legal minimum for one person to live on.
법적 최소 기준을 거의 충족하지 못함 한 사람이 살아가기 위해.
And if Min-suk finds out about this,
그리고 민석이가 이 사실을 알게 된다면
the minimum cost of living will be the least of my problems.
최소 생활비 내 문제 중 가장 작은 문제일 것입니다.
What? Why?
무엇? 왜?
You got more to say?
더 할 말이 있나요?
Sir.
선생님.
Would you mind if I took a half-day
반나절 정도 시간을 투자해도 괜찮을까요?
and left early today?
그리고 오늘 일찍 떠났어?
NOTICE TO APPEAR
출석 통지
SUSPECT INTERROGATION REPORT
용의자 심문 보고서
Your name is Kang Sang-ung, correct?
이름이 강상웅 맞죠?
Yes.
예.
NAME: KANG SANG-UNG
이름: 강상웅
No need to answer directly.
직접적으로 대답할 필요는 없습니다.
It's just a name.
그것은 단지 이름일 뿐입니다.
It could work against you.
그것은 당신에게 불리하게 작용할 수 있습니다.
Just saying my name?
내 이름만 말하면 돼?
You saw our faces at the community center, didn't you?
당신은 우리의 얼굴을 보았다 주민센터에 있지, 그렇지?
My client says
내 고객이 말하길
that he doesn't recall.
그가 기억하지 못한다는 것입니다.
I feel like a chaebol chairman at a hearing.
재벌 회장이 된 기분 청문회에서.
- You're here. - Yeah.
- 여기 있어요. - 응.
Wait outside.
밖에서 기다리세요.
It's been a while.
오랜만이에요.
I knew it was you.
나는 그것이 당신이라는 것을 알았습니다.
Are you still doing that crap?
아직도 그런 짓을 하고 있나요?
Of course.
물론.
Someone has to.
누군가는 그래야 합니다.
Is it this guy this time?
이번엔 이 사람인가?
- Hey! - Yes?
- 여기요! - 예?
What the hell were you thinking?
대체 무슨 생각을 한 거야?
You're married.
당신은 결혼했어요.
What are you, a cop? A firefighter?
당신은 경찰입니까? 소방관?
No, I'm just nobody--
아니, 난 그냥 아무도 아니야--
Let me give you some advice.
몇 가지 조언을 드리겠습니다.
Stop this.
그만둬.
If you cause trouble one more time, I swear I'll put you in jail.
한 번 더 문제를 일으키면 맹세코 당신을 감옥에 가두겠습니다.
Do you understand?
이해했나요?
Do you know that police officer?
그 경찰관을 아시나요?
- He was a member of the society. - Superpowers?
-그는 사회의 일원이었습니다. - 초능력?
Really?
정말?
What was his superpower?
그의 초능력은 무엇이었나요?
Picking fights.
싸움을 따기.
By the way,
그런데,
why is he trying to capture me?
그 사람은 왜 나를 잡으려고 하는 걸까?
- Is he with the Mundane Vanguard? - Our beliefs don't quite align.
- 그 사람이 몬데인 뱅가드 소속인가요? - 우리의 신념은 완전히 일치하지 않습니다.
It's fine. No worries.
괜찮습니다. 걱정 마세요.
But I'm worried about it.
그러나 나는 그것이 걱정된다.
- He said he'd put me in jail-- - I told you, it's fine!
- 그는 나를 감옥에 가둘 거라고 했어요-- - 내가 말했잖아, 괜찮아!
I'm good. I'm cutting carbs these days.
난 괜찮아. 요즘 탄수화물을 줄이고 있어요.
What a load of crap.
정말 쓰레기가 많아요.
Take care of your health too.
건강도 챙기세요.
Gotta live a long life.
오래 살아야 합니다.
You're just like you were when you were a kid.
당신은 당신과 똑같습니다 당신이 어렸을 때.
Prattling on and running your mouth.
횡설수설하고 입을 다물고 있습니다.
Damn, I should have killed you back then.
젠장, 그때 널 죽였어야 했는데.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
I drugged them.
나는 그들에게 약을 먹였습니다.
With the one that replicates superpowers.
초능력을 복제하는 것과 함께.
How do you know about that?
그것에 대해 어떻게 알 수 있나요?
Of course I know. I'm family too.
물론 알아요. 나도 가족이에요.
Think of it as a large-scale clinical trial.
생각해 보세요 대규모 임상시험으로.
It's been on the news all day long.
하루 종일 뉴스에 나왔어요.
What good does it do us to draw attention?
관심을 끄는 것이 우리에게 무슨 소용이 있습니까?
Dad.
아빠.
That bastard is doing it on purpose. He wants us to go down.
저 새끼는 일부러 그러는 거야. 그는 우리가 내려가기를 원해요.
You're right.
당신 말이 맞아요.
I did it on purpose. So that Kang Sang-ung could see.
일부러 그랬어요. 강상웅이 볼 수 있도록.
What kind of bullshit is that?
그게 무슨 헛소리야?
Father. Do you know what the true essence of a hero is?
아버지. 당신은 알고 있나요 영웅의 진정한 본질은 무엇인가?
It's meddling.
간섭이에요.
Caring about things that aren't even theirs.
사물에 대한 배려 그것은 그들의 것도 아닙니다.
Not being able to ignore what bothers them.
무시할 수 없다는 것 무엇이 그들을 괴롭히는가.
He will come for me soon.
그는 곧 나를 데리러 올 것이다.
At a time and a place that works best for me.
시간과 장소에 그게 나에게 가장 잘 맞는다.
From now on,
지금부터,
you take over the lab.
당신이 연구실을 맡아요.
Wait, Dad.
잠깐만요, 아빠.
When blood runs in the streets,
거리에 피가 흘렀을 때,
our coffers fill.
우리 금고가 가득 차 있습니다.
Let's eat.
먹자.
So you were questioned by the cops?
그래서 경찰서에서 심문을 받았나요?
Even if you end up in prison, don't mention our names.
감옥에 갇히더라도 우리 이름은 언급하지 마세요.
I told you to stop joking around.
농담하지 말라고 했어요.
I'm really serious.
난 정말 진지해요.
You read everything I handed out, right?
내가 나눠준 걸 다 읽었지?
This is the clinical trial list.
임상시험 목록입니다.
Six of them jumped off yesterday.
그 중 6명이 어제 뛰어내렸습니다.
The Mundane Vanguard is testing on civilians.
평범한 선봉대 민간인을 대상으로 테스트 중입니다.
MUNDANE
평범한
The experiments are centered around the clubs in Gangnam.
실험이 중심에 있습니다. 강남 클럽 주변
Apparently, it's popular for its intense hallucinations.
분명히 인기가 있는 것 같군요 강렬한 환각 때문입니다.
A dealer called Hermes is the supplier.
Hermes라는 딜러가 공급업체입니다.
Their name is Hermes?
이름이 헤르메스인가요?
HERMES AT CLUB MECENAT
클럽 메세나의 에르메스
A different color designer bag every day.
매일 다른 색상의 디자이너 가방.
I got intel that Hermes will be at Club Mecenat tomorrow afternoon.
헤르메스가 될 것이라는 정보를 얻었습니다. 내일 오후 클럽 메세나에서
We catch Hermes as fast as we can and retrieve the drugs.
우리는 가능한 한 빨리 헤르메스를 잡습니다. 그리고 약을 회수하세요.
Once the trials are over, they'll start replicating and selling superpowers.
시험이 끝나면 시작됩니다. 초능력을 복제하고 판매합니다.
At all costs, before there are more casualties...
무슨 수를 써서라도, 더 많은 사상자가 발생하기 전에...
we must stop them.
우리는 그들을 막아야 합니다.
HOTTEST AFFORDABLE SPEC-UP NOW IN BULK DEALER: HERMES
지금 가장 저렴하고 저렴한 사양을 대량으로 만나보세요 딜러: 헤르메스
I'm home.
나는 집에있다.
Hey.
여기요.
What's all this? Are we moving?
이게 다 뭐야? 우리 이사가는 거야?
Take your clothes off.
옷을 벗으세요.
- Right now? - Yes.
- 지금 바로? - 예.
I don't have any cash.
현금이 없어요.
Should I go get some?
가서 좀 사야 하나?
What are you thinking? We need to pick tomorrow's outfit.
당신은 무엇을 생각하고 있습니까? 내일 입을 옷을 골라야 해요.
Oh, that's right. The family meeting.
아, 그렇군요. 가족 회의.
Why didn't you answer your phone? Something happen?
왜 전화를 받지 않았나요? 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
No, my phone was in my bag. Sorry.
아니, 내 휴대폰은 가방 안에 있었어. 죄송합니다.
It has to go smoothly.
순조롭게 진행되어야 합니다.
The marriage plans got messed up.
결혼 계획이 엉망이 되었습니다.
Marriage registration, housing lottery, proposal, then parents meeting each other.
결혼등록, 주택추첨, 프로포즈를 한 후 부모님들이 서로 만나는 것입니다.
If this meeting goes badly,
이 회의가 안 좋아지면
everything that Min-suk and I have worked towards will go down the drain.
민석이와 내가 가진 모든 것 노력하면 물거품이 될 것입니다.
All right. This one's the best.
알았어. 이게 최고야.
- Go try it on. - Okay.
- 가서 입어보세요. - 좋아요.
This looks pretty good.
이것은 꽤 좋아 보인다.
Hey, this is so expensive. Why did you buy it?
이야, 이거 너무 비싸. 왜 샀어요?
Our families will be meeting. Don't wear it too often.
우리 가족이 만날 거예요. 너무 자주 입지 마세요.
1.29 million won?
129만원?
You don't even spend this much on your own clothes.
이렇게까지 돈도 안 쓰잖아 자신의 옷에.
Everything good lately?
최근에는 좋은 일이 있나요?
Yeah, of course. All good.
응, 물론이지. 모두 좋습니다.
You look great. 7:00 p.m. at Jongno.
당신은 멋져 보인다. 오후 7시 종로에서.
Don't be late.
늦지 마세요.
All right.
괜찮은.
Here.
여기.
- If traffic's bad, I'll just fly there. - What?
- 교통이 안 좋으면 그냥 비행기 타고 갈게요. - 무엇?
I'm giving it to you just in case. Try not to use it.
만약을 대비해 당신에게 주겠어요. 그것을 사용하지 마십시오.
All right.
괜찮은.
- Can you give me 50,000 won more? - No.
- 5만원 더 주실 수 있나요? - 아니.
Okay.
알았어.
- See you later. - Okay.
- 나중에 봐요. - 좋아요.
Bye.
안녕.
I'm off.
나는 떠난다.
One hour from Gangnam to Jongno.
강남에서 종로까지 1시간
Catch Hermes by 6:00 p.m.
오후 6시까지 헤르메스를 만나세요
and make it to the dinner at 7:00 p.m.
그리고 오후 7시에 저녁 식사를 하러 갑니다
I can do this.
난 할 수 있어.
Where are you?
당신은 어디에 있나요?
We're in.
들어왔습니다.
Clubbing on the day our parents are meeting?
당일 클럽 활동 우리 부모님은 만나시나요?
Unbelievable.
말도 안 돼요.
What's with your outfit?
당신의 의상은 무엇입니까?
Says the one dressed for an old-school nightclub.
옷을 입은 사람이 말하길 구식 나이트클럽의 경우.
An old-school nightclub? Hey, this is an expensive outfit.
구식 나이트클럽? 이야, 이거 비싼 옷이구나.
They're all so passionate about their lives.
그들은 모두 너무 열정적이에요 그들의 삶에 대해.
Where did you get that?
그거 어디서 났어?
That bar is selling it.
저 바가 팔고 있어요.
The bracelet allows you up to 5,000 won for free.
팔찌는 당신을 허용합니다 최대 5,000원까지 무료입니다.
Honestly, shouldn't stuff like this be covered by the budget?
솔직히 이런거 하면 안되는데 예산으로 감당할 수 있나요?
I mean, we're always using our own money.
내 말은, 우리는 항상 우리 자신의 돈을 사용하고 있다는 것입니다.
Don't drink this.
이거 마시지 마세요.
What's the priciest here? Order it.
여기서 가장 비싼 것은 무엇입니까? 주문하세요.
That's 100 million.
1억입니다.
Just drink this.
이것만 마셔요.
So how are we supposed to find Hermes?
그렇다면 헤르메스를 어떻게 찾아야 할까요?
ATTORNEY BYEON IMAGE SENT
변 변호사 이미지 전송됨
FIND A RED BAG
빨간 가방 찾기
He wants us to find a red bag.
그 사람은 우리가 빨간 가방을 찾아주길 원해요.
Red?
빨간색?
Red...
빨간색...
I'm sorry. My mistake. I'm really sorry.
미안해요. 내 실수. 정말 죄송해요.
That shape...
그 모양...
I'm sorry.
미안해요.
Damn it. So many red bags...
젠장. 빨간 가방이 너무 많아서...
They all look so similar.
모두 너무 비슷해 보이네요.
It's confusing.
혼란스럽네요.
That one.
그거.
- That's it, isn't it? - It is.
- 그게 다야, 그렇지? - 그것은.
- Are you fucking nuts? Crazy bastard. - What the fuck?
- 너 미쳤어? 미친 놈. - 도대체 뭐야?
You should just go today.
오늘은 그냥 가셔야 해요.
Your next order will be free.
다음 주문은 무료입니다.
Let's go, damn it.
가자, 젠장.
Perfect.
완벽해요.
I can make it to the meeting on time.
나는 제시간에 회의에 참석할 수 있습니다.
You're Hermes, aren't you?
당신은 헤르메스죠, 그렇죠?
Mr. Kang Sang-ung?
강상웅씨요?
I have some business with you.
나는 당신과 볼일이 있어요.
You made it all the way here.
여기까지 오셨습니다.
Honestly, I didn't think you could.
솔직히, 나는 당신이 할 수 있다고 생각하지 않았습니다.
What business? Tell me.
무슨 사업? 말해 주세요.
She's speaking informally now.
그녀는 지금 비공식적으로 말하고 있습니다.
If things go wrong, I might be a bit late.
일이 잘못되면 조금 늦을 수도 있습니다.
I didn't know you were one of us.
나는 당신이 우리 중 하나라는 것을 몰랐습니다.
Wanna join the society too?
나도 사회에 참여하고 싶나요?
We have tea and snacks on weekends. I'll give you a sign-up form.
주말에는 차와 간식을 먹습니다. 가입 양식을 드리겠습니다.
Is this all you carry around?
들고다니는 게 이게 다야?
I recently got a pay cut.
최근에 급여가 삭감되었습니다.
So things have been tough.
그래서 상황이 힘들었습니다.
You can never join the society now.
이제 절대로 사회에 합류할 수 없습니다.
Managing Director Jo Nathan wants me to bring you over.
조 네이선 전무이사 내가 당신을 데려오길 원해요.
That might be difficult.
어려울 수도 있습니다.
I have an important appointment later.
나중에 중요한 약속이 있어요.
Hey.
여기요.
Just hit me!
그냥 때려!
I won't be able to see her anyway.
어쨌든 그녀를 볼 수는 없을 것 같아요.
Hey, mister!
안녕하세요 아저씨!
- This is nuts. - What?
- 이건 말도 안 되는 소리야. - 무엇?
What's with your clothes?
당신의 옷은 무엇입니까?
Mr. Attorney.
변호사님.
- Yes? - Hermes is a superhuman.
- 예? - 헤르메스는 초인적 존재입니다.
I've got the drugs, so we'll hurry out.
나한테 약이 있으니 서둘러 나가자.
Really? A superhuman?
정말? 초인적?
Yes, stay sharp.
예, 예의를 지키세요.
Let's get out of here.
여기서 나가자.
What? Because I told you to let him hit you?
무엇? 내가 말했으니까 그 사람이 널 때리게 하려고?
If that's all he's got, I think I can bring him in myself.
그 사람이 가진 게 그게 전부라면, 내 생각엔 내가 직접 그를 데려올 수 있을 것 같아.
That would be no fun.
그건 재미없을 거예요.
- I'm sorry. - Coming through!
- 죄송합니다. - 지나가고 있어요!
Coming through, excuse us.
가는 중입니다. 실례합니다.
What the hell?
대체 뭐야?
- What's this? - What the hell?
- 이게 뭐죠? - 대체 뭐야?
What's this? Some kind of surprise?
이건 뭐죠? 일종의 놀라움?
What the hell?
대체 뭐야?
FOR YOU, WHO WORKS FOR OTHERS EVEN WITHOUT RECOGNITION
다른 사람을 위해 일하는 당신을 위해 인식하지 못하더라도
It's Jo Nathan.
조 네이선이에요.
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
Clubs aren't usually like this, are they?
클럽은 보통 이런 곳 아니죠?
Everyone wants to be someone special.
누구나 특별한 사람이 되고 싶어합니다.
What is this?
이것은 무엇입니까?
YOU CAN BE SPECIAL TOO
당신도 특별해질 수 있다
We should go.
우리는 가야 해요.
But speaking from experience,
하지만 경험을 토대로 말하면
I swear,
맹세합니다
there's nothing better than living a normal life.
더 나은 건 없어요 평범한 삶을 사는 것보다
- Bun-mi! - Hey, get him!
- 분미! - 이봐, 잡아!
Hey, get out of the way!
이봐, 비켜라!
Give it here! Get lost, you fucking bitch!
여기로 주세요! 꺼져라, 이 빌어먹을 년아!
Let go! Come on!
가자! 어서 해봐요!
Seriously!
진지하게!
Get him!
그를 잡아!
Hey, give me that!
야, 그거 줘!
You fucking bitch!
이 빌어먹을 년!
It's my bag!
내 가방이야!
Give me that! Move!
그거 줘! 이동하다!
No!
아니요!
Fuck! No!
못쓰게 만들다! 아니요!
If the drugs get taken away, everyone will die.
마약을 없애면 모두가 죽을 것이다.
No.
아니요.
Being broke is a crime.
파산하는 것은 범죄입니다.
Look at him.
그를보세요.
He can't do anything without money.
그는 돈이 없으면 아무것도 할 수 없습니다.
No.
아니요.
Sang-ung.
상웅.
Bun-mi!
분미!
MY MIN-SUK
마이민석
The person you called is unavailable. Please leave a message--
전화하신 분은 부재중입니다. 메시지를 남겨주세요--
Looks like I chose the wrong day...
날짜를 잘못 선택한 것 같네요...
for our parents to meet.
부모님을 만나기 위해
Subtitle translation by: Yun-hee Jang
자막번역 : 장윤희